<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<news>
  <item>
    <id>1</id>
    <date>2020-03-19 11AM (PST)</date>
    <subject>News Section!</subject>
    <text>In order to do a better job of announcing changes in the game,
      I've added a "News" section which will be displayed during
      login.  It should only display news that you haven't seen yet,
      and you can use "Q" to quit out of the news display early.

      If you want to see the news items at any point once in the
      game, use the NEWS command.</text>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>2</id>
    <date>2020-03-19 12PM (PST)</date>
    <subject>Bug fixes</subject>
    <text>- The rat warren is now designated NO_SAVE
      This means you cannot use SAVE or QUIT (or any other command
      which causes the character to be saved) in these locations.
      (This is to avoid camping mobs that drop loot / SP)
      - Character facing direction is now saved
      - New characters will enter the game facing west
      - Added the following frames for the renderer:
        - Drawbridge
        - Porcullis
        - Short Walls
      - Fixed typos in 2nd level of South Gatehouse Tower
      - Paginated HELP, STATS (and more to come)
      - Fixed crash when player stumbled
      - Lowered the weight of keys
      - Only 1/2 of equipped item weight is counted towards
        encumbrance penalty</text>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>3</id>
    <date>2020-03-19 4:30PM (PST)</date>
    <subject>Effects are now in the game!</subject>
    <text>There are 2 kinds of "effects" currently implemented:
      1. Stat effects: like +1 DEXTERITY or +2 AGILITY
      This kind of effect increases a base stat and that increase
      can be noticed in related skills that use the stat or
      whenever that stat is checked (such as a stumble roll, etc).
      2. Skill effects: like +5 AXE or +10 CLUB skill
      This kind of effect directly increases the skill so that
      actions with that skill will be more successful than without
      the effect.
      
      Currently, there is only 1 item in the game that has an
      effect. However, it had to be broken in order to fix effects
      in general. If you have this item you can see "(broken
      effect)". Unfortunately, you'll need to discard the broken
      item and get it again from the original location.</text>
  </item>
</news>
<!--
# vim: tabstop=2 shiftwidth=2 expandtab:
//-->
